Look, Scott. This is a photograph I took during my trip to Australia.
看,这是我到澳大利亚旅行时拍的一张照片.
Let me see it, Mike.
让我看看,Mike.
This is a good photograph.
这是一张很好的照片.
Who are these people?
这些人是谁?
They're people I met during the trip.
他们是我旅行时认识的人.
That's the ship we travelled on.
那是我们所乘的那条船.
What a beautiful ship!
多漂亮的船啊!
Who's this?
这是谁?
That's the man I told you about.
这就是我跟你说过的那个人.
Remember?
还记得吗?
Ah yes.
啊,记得.
The one who offered you a job in Australia.
就是给你提供了一份在澳大利亚的工作的那个人.
That's right.
对.
Who's this?
这是谁?
Guess!
你猜!
It's not you, is it?
这不是你,对吗?
That's right.
是我.
I grew a beard during the trip.
我在旅行时留了胡子,
but I shaved it off when I came home.
但我回到家时把它刮了.
Why did you shave it off?
你为什么把它刮了?
My wife didn't like it!
我妻子不喜欢它!